A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Client Correspondence and Card File, 1921-1968.
  - West Point High School, - CCN 923 1964 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Westhampton College, - CCN 886 1946 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 835
  - Westhaven Elementary School, - CCN 887 1953 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 1149
  - Westminster Presbyterian Church, - CCN 889 1953 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Westover Theatre, - CCN 922 1950 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Wheelwright, Mrs.Thomas S.- CCN 890 1942-1946 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 9
  - White, George- CCN 891 1960-1961 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2268
  - White, G. T.- CCN 892 1957 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 2157
  - White, William H., Jr.- CCN 896 1942-1960 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 494
  - White, Mrs.W. Temple- CCN 894 1959 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Gillette account number: 2247
  - White Memorial Presbyterian Church, - CCN 893 1951-1957 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    Gillette account number: 1060
  - Whitehouse, Mrs. L. B.- CCN 895 1948-1954 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    Gillette account number: 523
  - Whiting, Giles- CCN 994 n.d. (Box 71, Folder 27)
    Gillette account number: 271
  - Whittet, R. McLean, Jr.- CCN 898 1954 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    Gillette account number: 856
  - Whittet, R. McLean, Sr.- CCN 897 1947-1968 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Gillette account number: 2398
  - Wilborne, J. A.- CCN 899 1950 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    Gillette account number: 1004
  - Wilkinson, E. C.- CCN 900 1943 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Wilkinson, Mrs.Frank S.- CCN 901 1943-1948 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Wilkinson, J. Harvie, Jr.- CCN 902 1957-1958 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2143
  - Wilkinson, J. Harvie, Jr.- CCN 902 1959-1966 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Will, Mrs.Erwin H.- CCN 903 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2269
  - William and Mary College, - CCN 904 1942-1953 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 180
  - William and Mary College- Norfolk Extension, - CCN 905 1948-1952 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 509
  - Williams, Dr. Carrington, Jr.- CCN 1094 n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1131
  - Williams, Cranston- CCN 906 1958-1967 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2217
  - Williams, Mrs.E. Randolph- CCN 907 1942-1948 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 291
  - Williams, Mrs.E. Victor- CCN 908 1941-1953 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 368
  - Williams, Mrs.Fielding- CCN 909 1942-1964 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 859
  - Williams, Miss Joanna- CCN 910 1942-1952 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 572
  - Williams, Dr.Richard K.- CCN 911 1963 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2368
  - Williams, T. C. (See also Morton, Dr. David C.)- CCN 912 1958-1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 307
  - Williams, Thomas E.- CCN 969 n.d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2138
  - Williams, Truman G.- CCN 913 1942-1962 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 605
  - Williams, Mrs.Walter A.- CCN 914 1946-1967 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Mrs.Wyatt- CCN 915 1959-1967 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2277
  - Williamsburg (Colonial Williamsburg Foundation), - CCN 916 1947-1951 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Mrs.Mary Lewis- CCN 917 1959-1963 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2302
  - Wilson, Mrs.Mary Lewis- CCN 917 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Mrs.Norwood- CCN 918 1954-1955 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2286
  - Wilson, Robert A.- CCN 919 1965 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2436
  - Wilson, Thomas A. (Also Wilson, John T. and Price, Mrs. G.H.)- CCN 1122 n.d. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 535
  - Wilton (Colonial Dames), - CCN 1221 1942-1943 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 456
  - Winslow, J. Norman- CCN 920 1949-1951 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 930
  - Winstead, J.- CCN 921 1952 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Winter, Mrs.Edna R.- CCN 924 1950 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Winter Park Presbyterian Church, - CCN 925 1958 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Wise, John Dana- CCN 926 n.d. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Withers, Lawson- CCN 927 1956 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Witt, Luke- CCN 928 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2476
  - Womack, Charles A.- CCN 929 1951-1951 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1046
  - Woman's Club, Richmond, VA, - CCN 930 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2495
  - Wood, Kenneth- CCN 931 1942-1950 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 737
  - Woodard, Mrs.David W.- CCN 932 1949-1952 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Woodard, Mrs.Windsor W.- CCN 933 1942-1945 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 956
  - Woodberry Forest School, - CCN 934 1947-1964 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 487
  - Woodcock, Mrs. S. Franklyn- CCN 935 1952 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 1094
  - Woodrow Wilson High School, - CCN 936 1950 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 977
  - Wooten, Mrs. Sterling Dillon- CCN 937 1957-1968 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Wooten, Mrs. W. I.- CCN 939 1946-1947 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Wooten Subdivision, - CCN 938 1947-1953 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 1158
  - Worley, Mrs. Corinna M.- CCN 940 1949 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 963
  - Wright, Thomas F.- CCN 941 1945-1952 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 849
  - Wythe Corporation, - CCN 942 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Yeaman's Motor Court, - CCN 943 n.d. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Yorktown Manor Hotel and Country Club, - CCN 1213 1925 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Young, William A.- CCN 944 1955 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 1160
  - Zimmerman, Mrs.A. V.- CCN 945 1952 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Zimmer, W. L.- CCN 946 1965 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2437
  - Zinn, Mrs. F. C.- CCN 952 1942-1963 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 59
  - Zinn, Mrs. George - Cemetery, - CCN 953 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 435
  - Zoll, E. J.- CCN 947 1963 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2380
  - Card File, A-Ca (Box 76)
  - Card File, Ce-El (Box 77)
  - Card File, Em-Ha (Box 78)
  - Card File, Ha-Mc (Box 79)
  - Card File, Me-Po (Box 80)
  - Card File, Po-Sh (Box 81)
  - Card File, Sh-V (Box 82)
  - Card File, W-Z (Box 83)
- Drawings, 1902-1968.
  Series III is housed in 531 archival drawings tubes and arranged by Client Control Number (CCN), an institutionally imposed numbering system. The series includes sketches, perspective drawings, renderings, plot plans, surveys, plans, architectural blueprints, and planting lists. The majority of the drawings were produced in Gillette's office by his draftsmen. Some projects include architectural drawings for structures, mostly residences, associated with a particular project. Gillette worked closely with several architects, most notably William Lawrence Bottomley. The drawings in this series are executed on bumwad, heavy paper, linen, and the like. Copies may be found in blueprint, Diazo print, inkjet or electrostatic print. Many of the drawings are colored with colored pencil and ink giving them an artistic quality. A project may be housed on several tubes, or several projects may be housed on one tube, depending on the volume of materials. Additionally, various types of architectural drawings and reproductions can chemically interact with one another. To avoid potential loss of information or damage to the drawings, certain of these drawing types have been separated on the rolls by sheets of buffer paper. It is imperative that these remain segregated when returned to the roll.
  Due to the size of this series, a container listing has not been included in this finding aid. Instead, a searchable database has been created to aid the researcher in using this collection. The database's web-interface can be found on the Gillette Drawings and Correspondence Database. The database can be searched by Drawing Description, Gillette Account Number, Client Control Number, and Client Name. The Drawing Description field is searchable by keywords in the title of the drawing. Typically, this will include a description of the drawing (e.g. "Planting Plan") and the client's name. The page also includes a drop-down list of clients organized alphabetically by the last name of the client or the business name. General searches, such as a Client Name search of "Jones," returns a list of results containing links that will take the researcher to the full listing for that client name or client control number. If correspondence exists for a particular project, the results will also return a reference to those materials. Correspondence does not survive for all projects. Likewise, drawings do not survive for each project and in some cases only correspondence results are returned. It is important to note that not all of Gillette's materials survive and a search may yield no results.
  Arranged by Client Control Number (CCN).
- Housing Projects, 1924-1960 (bulk 1939-1955).
  Series IV is housed in 10 archival boxes on shelf and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are correspondence, manuals, specifications, and federal government bulletins relative to Gillette's work on public housing projects. These materials were treated as a separate series and are therefore not included in Series II: Client Correspondence. However, drawings for these projects, if they exist, have been organized in Series III: Drawings. Before and following World War II, Gillette did extensive work on public housing projects as many of his wealthier clients scaled down or eliminated their plans for large landscape projects. Reflected in this series are projects from Virginia (Richmond, Newport News, Portsmouth, Hopewell, Bristol, Lynchburg, Camp Pendleton, and Fort Story); North Carolina (Rocky Mount); and New Jersey (Asbury Park and Long Branch).
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1939 Feb-Jun (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1939 Jly-Dec (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1940 Jan-Jun (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1940 Jly-Dec (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1941 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, Housing Authority, Correspondence, 1942 and n.d. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-1) and (VA 2-2),Correspondence, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-1) and (VA 2-2),Correspondence, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-1) and (VA 2-2),Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-1) and (VA 2-2),Correspondence, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-3) William L. Rice Terrace Extension, Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Bristol, VA, Housing Projects (VA 2-3) William L. Rice Terrace Extension, Specifications, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Camp Pendleton and Fort Story, VA, Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Hopewell, VA, Housing Projects (VA 5-2) and (VA 5-3), Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Hopewell, VA, Housing Projects (VA 5-2) and (VA 5-3), Construction Specifications, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Hopewell, VA, Housing Projects (VA 5-2) and (VA 5-3), Lawns and Plantings Specifications, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Hopewell, VA, Housing Projects (VA 5-2) and (VA 5-3), Miscellaneous Documents, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Long Branch, NJ, Garfield Court, Correspondence, 1939 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Long Branch, NJ, Garfield Court, Correspondence, 1940 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Long Branch, NJ, Garfield Court, Correspondence, 1941 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Lynchburg, VA, Housing Project (VA 13-1), Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Lynchburg, VA, Housing Project (VA 13-1), Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Newport News, VA, Housing Projects (VA 3-4) and (VA 3-5), Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Portsmouth, VA, Housing Projects (VA 1-4) and (VA 1-5), Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Portsmouth, VA, Housing Projects (VA 1-4) and (VA 1-5), Construction Specifications (VA 1-5), 1953 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Portsmouth, VA, Housing Projects (VA 1-4) and (VA 1-5), Lawns and Planting Specifications (VA 1-5), 1953 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Public Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Subdivision Ordinances and Information, 1924-1954 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Public Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Site Engineering Bulletins- Public Housing Administration, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Public Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Neighborhood Standards Bulletin- Federal Housing Administration, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Public Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Minimum Property Standards- Federal Housing Administration, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Public Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Minimum Property Standards- Federal Housing Administration, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Correspondence, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Correspondence, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Construction Specifications, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, VA, Hillside Court (VA 7-4) and Creighton Court (VA 7-5), Planting Specifications, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Richmond, VA, Gilpin Court Extension, Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Richmond, VA, Gilpin Court Extension, Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Richmond, VA, Gilpin Court Extension, Construction Specifications, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Richmond, VA, Gilpin Court Extension, Neighborhood Standards Bulletin- Virginia-Federal Housing Administration, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Richmond, VA, Gilpin Court Extension, Planting Specifications, 1955-1957 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, VA, Mosby Court (VA 7-8), Correspondence, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Richmond, VA, Mosby Court (VA 7-8), Correspondence, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Richmond, VA, Mosby Court (VA 7-8), Correspondence, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Richmond, VA, Mosby Court (VA 7-8), Correspondence, 1963 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Richmond, VA, Mosby Court (VA 7-8), Correspondence, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, VA, Whitcomb Court (VA 7-6), Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Rocky Mount, NC, Housing Project (19-1), Correspondence, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Rocky Mount, NC, Housing Project (19-2), Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Rocky Mount, NC, Housing Projects (19-3) and (19-4), Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Rocky Mount, NC, Housing Projects- Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Maps, 1883-1961.
  Series V is housed in one (1) map case drawer and arranged alphabetically by locality (town/city). The series consists mainly of subdivision plans, park layouts, and perspective drawings for various projects across the United States. Heavily represented is the work of the Olmstead Brothers firm of Brookline, Massachusetts. It is unclear whether Gillette participated in any of these projects during his time in Boston or whether these were simply reference materials that he maintained in his office. Three (3) drawings are signed as being traced by Gillette and date from the time period that he began to strike out on his own in Richmond, Virginia. These materials seem to be unrelated to any of Gillette's known projects.
  Arranged alphabetically by state and there under by city.
  - AL- Birmingham, Outline Map Showing Present and Proposed Park Areas Within the City- 1924 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 37 x 61 cm.
  - AL- Birmingham, Outline Plan of Proposed Park System for Birmingham [2 copies]- 1924 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 45 x 40 cm.
  - AL- Birmingham, Howard College Preliminary Site Plan- 1947 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 37 x 70 cm.
  - AL- Troy, General Plan for Troy State Teachers College- 1930 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 43 x 57 cm.
  - Bermuda- Tuckers Town, Bermuda Development Company Ltd. Preliminary Plan or Mid-Ocean Club [2 copies]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 21 x 46 cm.
  - CA- Los Angeles County, Palos Verdes Estates- 1924 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Directors of Design; Size: 71 x 107 cm.
  - CA- Los Angeles County, The Developed Area of Palos Verdes Estates [2 copies]- 1927 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Directors of Design; Size: 28 x 43 cm.
  - CA- Palo Alto, Topographical Map of All Lands Situated in Santa Clara Co. Belonging to Leland Stanford Jr., University at Palo Alto, CA- 1887 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Drawn by: Surveyed at the Request of F.L. Olmsted L.A.; Size: 56 x 71 cm.
  - CA- Santa Cruz, General Plan for Pasatiempo Country Club and Estates- 1929 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects; Size: 32 x 61 cm.
  - CO- Broadmoor, General Plan for Broadmoor Hotel [2 copies]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 33 x 34 cm.
  - CO- Douglas County., Design Map of the Village of Lake Wauconda- 1890 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 72 x 72 cm.
  - CT- New Haven, City Improvement Committee New Haven Plan to Accompany Report of Improvement Commission- 1909 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    Drawn by: Cass Gilbert, Architect - F.L. Olmsted, Landscape Architect; Size: 58 x 65 cm.
  - CT- Waterbury, General Plan for Coeacres- 1929 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 36 x 63 cm.
  - DC- Washington, Preliminary Plan for Laying Out Buildings and Grounds of the American University- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 44 x 56 cm.
  - DC- Washington, Map of the District of Columbia...- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Commission on the Improvement of the, Park System; Size: 72 x 76 cm.
  - DC- Washington, General Plan for the Improvement of the U.S. Capitol Grounds- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 51 x 38 cm.
  - DC- Washington, Map of the Tidal Waters of the Potomac River- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 27 x 21 cm.
  - FL- Boca Grande, Boca Grande, FL, Plan for Gulf Section- 1924 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 44 x 74 cm.
  - FL- Polk County., Preliminary Plan Mountain Lake Polk County, FL- 1916 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Drawn by: Prepared for the Mountain Lake Corporation, by Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 38 x 43 cm.
  - GA- Augusta, General Plan for the Augusta National Golf Club [2 copies]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 46 x 46 cm.
  - IL- Chicago, Map of the Buildings & Grounds of the World's Columbian Exposition Chicago, Ills, U.S.A. [2 copies]- 1893 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: Issued by the, Department of Public Works; Size: 64 x 68 cm.
  - IL- Chicago, General Plan of Jackson Park- 1905 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 46 x 61 cm.
  - KY- Louisville, General Plan for Boone Square- 1892 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted & Co. - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 55 x 48 cm.
  - KY- Louisville, General Plan for Iroquois Park- 1897 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: F.L. and J.C. Olmsted, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 74 x 117 cm.
  - KY- Louisville, Design Map for Alta Vista...- 1900 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 50 x 72 cm.
  - KY- Louisville, General Plan for Central Park- 1904 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 31 x 31 cm.
  - MA- Andover, Plan of Real Estate Belonging to Philips Academy- 1891 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Melvin B. Smith, Civil Engineer & Surveyor, Lowell, Mass.; Size: 53 x 66 cm.
  - MA- Andover, Phillips Academy Map of Property- 1929 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 23 x 33 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Park Department - City of Boston Map of Proposed Arboretum...- 1879 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Fredk. Law Olmstead, Landscape Architect; Size: 48 x 61 cm.
  - MA- Boston, General Plan of Franklin Park- 1885 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: F.L. & J.C. Olmsted, Landscape Architects; Size: 56 x 71 cm.
  - MA- Boston, General Plan of Franklin Park- 1891 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: F.L. & J.C. Olmsted, Landscape Architects, Advisory; Size: 63 x 66 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Plan of the Parkway From Jamaica Park to Franklin Park- 1892 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted and Co. landscape Architects; Size: 24 x 62 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Metropolitan Park Commission Charles River Reservation Boston, Cambridge, Newton and Watertown [2 copies]- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Archts, Brookline, Mass; Size: 34 x 65 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Metropolitan Park Commission Mystic Valley Parkway General Plan- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Archts, Brookline, Mass; Size: 23 x 65 cm.
  - MA- Boston, General Plan of Franklin Park- 1896 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Fredk. Law Olmsted, Landscape Architect; Size: 61 x 77 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Metropolitan Park Commission Topographical Map of Stony Brook Reservation- 1896 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Wm. T. Pierce, Engineer; Size: 87 x 65 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Diagram of the Public Spaces of the Boston Metropolitan District in 1899 [2 copies]- 1899 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 37 x 37 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Sketch Plan of Public Reservations Upon the Banks of the Neponset River- 1899 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 41 x 118 cm.
  - MA- Boston, General Plan of Revere Beach Parkway- 1899 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 24 x 118 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Commonwealth of Massachusetts Map of the Metropolitan District of Boston Showing Local Public Reservations and Holdings of the Metropolitan Park Commission- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 63 x 71 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Plan for Subdivision of Property at Little Nahant Belonging to Sally M. Simmons- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)